Let's take a moment to clarify the meaning of
我们先来解释下
some words you might hear when discussing stock.
在讨论股票时可能会遇到的一些术语
A security is a financial instrument that has some type of monetary value.
证券是具有某种货币价值的金融工具
Some securities that you might have heard of are stocks, bonds, and options.
你可能听过的一些证券包括股票 债券和期权
Securities can be classified into three broad types;
证券主要分成三大类
debt securities, derivative securities, and equity securities.
债务证券 衍生证券和股权证券
Debt securities represent money that is owed and
债务证券表示持有人所有并且发债机构必须偿付的金额
must be repaid like government or corporate bonds,
例如政府或企业债券
or certificates of deposit.
或定期存款
Debt securities are also called fixed-income
债务证券也称为固定收益证券
securities because they promise a stream of income over
因为它们承诺以利息的形式
time in the form of interest either at
不断提供收益
a fixed rate or at a rate determined by a specific formula.
比如 固定利率 或者由特定的公式确定
Derivative securities such as options or futures contracts are
期权或期货合约等衍生证券之所以这么命名
so-named because their values depend on the prices of other assets.
是因为它们的价值取决于其他资产的价格
For example, an option is a contract which gives the buyer the right but not
期权是一种合约
the obligation to buy or sell
使买方有权在指定日期
an underlying asset at a specified price on a specified date.
以指定价格出售或购买标的资产 但是并非必须出售
An example of an option contract would be employee stock options.
期权合约包括员工认购股
As part of employee incentive programs,
作为一种员工激励计划
employers frequently offer employees the option to buy
企业经常向员工提供期权
companies stock at a lower price called the strike price,
员工有权以更低的价格（称为执行价格）购买公司股票
and later sell it on the open market to make a profit.
之后在公开市场上出售股票并获利
On the other hand, a futures contract obligates the buyer to buy or
另一方面 期货合约要求买方或卖方
the seller to sell an asset at a predetermined price at a specified time in the future.
在未来的指定日期以特定价格买入或卖出某项资产
For example, say, a dairy farmer concurrently sell milk for $2 a gallon.
例如 假设有个奶农目前以 2 美元/加仑出售牛奶
Next month, he plans to sell 200 gallons of milk,
下个月 他打算出售 200 加仑的牛奶
but he's concerned that fluctuations in the market price for milk will erode his profits.
但是 他担心牛奶的市场价格波动可能会降低利润
So he enters into a futures contract with an investor.
所以他与投资者达成了期货合约
By doing so, he is obligated to sell 200 gallons of milk on the agreed date,
所以他需要在约定的日期出售 200 加仑的牛奶
but he's guaranteed to receive $400 regardless of the market price of milk at that time.
但是无论到时候牛奶的市场价格是多少 他都能获得 400 美元
This type of agreement would protect him from the risk of
如果牛奶价格暴跌了
catastrophic loss if the price of milk tanks,
这种合约可以使他避免遭受巨额损失
but will also limit his ability to profit if the price of milk rises.
但是如果牛奶价格上涨了 他也没有机会提高利润
Then there's that last category, equity securities.
最后一个类别是股权证券
Let's break that phrase down.
我们拆分下这个术语
Equity is the value of an owned asset minus
股权是指所拥有资产的价值减去
the amount of all debts or liabilities on that asset.
该资产的所有债务或负债
So if you own a $15,000 car,
如果你拥有一辆价值 15,000 美元的汽车
but you owe a $5,000 loan against it,
但是贷款了 5,000 美元
the car represents $10,000 of equity.
那么该车的股权是 10,000 美元
The word equity can have somewhat different meanings in different contexts.
股权在不同的语境下有不同的含义
But in general, you can think of equity as the net value of something owned.
通常可以将股权看做所拥有的物品的净值
Stocks are called equity securities because they represent ownership in a firm.
股票称为股权证券 是因为它们代表对企业的所有权
One more thing, a security representing
此外 代表私有公司
ownership interest in a private company is called private equity.
所有权权益的证券称为私募股权